Hello Hi Welcome to my YouTube channel and
Radhe-Radhe everyone.  Today guys in this blog
I am sharing with you some
jewellery, [music] some outfits because the
festival seasons are coming.  So for this I have brought
for you very beautiful
[music] outfits reviews, demos,
you will get to see all these things in this blog.
So I will share with you
all the detailing of the products.  And first of all the
morning starts with my tea.
[Music] Then I
made bread pakoras for breakfast.  For which
I had prepared some ingredients.  Then
after that I prepared my
bread pakora.  You guys can see the
look of what it is like [MUSIC].  And
I always make green chutney with it.  So
for that, you can see tomatoes
and all the other [music]
products.
So it was prepared quickly.
[MUSIC] So you guys can see the
breakfast look.  This was my breakfast in the morning.
After that I am
sharing it with you all.  I got a surprise
gift which I am sharing with you all.
I share most of
my products
in my [music] videos.
So I'm showing you guys
what a gift I've received, and it's a
beautiful gift that you can gift to someone,
and there's a great [music]
lesson in this gift that we always
learn.  It said that we should
neither think bad about anyone nor see
nor tolerate [music].  One should always remain
cool and happy.  So I
really liked this gift along with this thought
[sangeet] which I got and you guys
can see that I have kept it near my TV
in the hall, so I really liked this
gift, after that I will share with you
today's main outfit looks [sangeet],
here I am sharing review plus demo of pay to pay outfits, so please
tell me how
I am looking in which outfit [sangeet].
So I am sharing all the outfits with you all.
Quickly, you guys
tell me in the comments which outfits
look good on me and let's see
which outfits I will wear because the
festival season is going on right now.  So that's why
I'm sharing the outfits [music] review with you guys.
You guys please tell me how
you liked it and if you have any
queries regarding it, if you want all the details of the product then
comment me.  I will
mention it in the description.  So let's
see what are the products.
So first of all let me show you guys.
Look at this.  This is a beautiful yellow
colored kurti.
This is a set of suits.  So, this is the top of it I'm
showing right now.  This is the top of this type.
It has this type of embroidery
and original glass is fitted in it.  Multi
colour embroidery work [music].
Its fabric is georgette fabric.
Its length is also a bit short.
Sleeveless is sleeveless.  But you get a separate sleeve
[music].  So there
is no tension.  You guys can attach the sleeves.
Look at this type.  It has original
mirror work and
is a great option for festivals.
You can see that its color is also very
good.  [Music]
So
whoever likes it, please comment.
I will mention its details to you all.
So its price is almost something like Rs 1300.  It was
something like 13 to 1500.  The outfit is completely plain from the back.  There
is work only on its top.
[MUSIC] The whole plane from the back.  But
this is a very beautiful set of suits.  Now let me
see, first of all I will look at it carefully, below it, there is a
design like the one with the cowrie shell.  [Music] Then
after that I am sharing its dupatta and the
sharara I got with it.
So first of all let me show you what its
Sharara looks like.  Its frill
is very nice.  So this type of
elastic is also found on top.  And
you guys should see its frill.  [MUSIC] Look how
much frill there is.  And its
design is also very beautiful.  The
look is great after wearing [music].  So
look how much frill it has and
look at the designs made in it.  Which
looks very beautiful.  After doing this,
its look becomes very good.
[MUSIC] It's also very nice in color.  These
types of colors look very good when worn.
So it is the best option for festivals.  The
colors look very good in this.
Now let me show you more of its dupatta.
This is its scarf.  Its
length is very good.  [Music]
You can see the length of it and it has this
kind of design on it.
[Music]
This is a very beautiful set.  So
[music] it has this kind of design on it.
You guys can see.  [MUSIC]
So it looked so beautiful.  And
I will also tell you guys the look after I vape it
[music]
what kind of look we get after vaping it.  And the next
suit is this one which has a very
beautiful color.  And there is embroidery in this also
because it was festival time.  So
both the outfits I have bought are
work based.  There are embroidery ones.   The
fabric [music] of this is net
fabric.  It has net fabric in it.  And
this type of design is found in its sleeves.
[Music] You get these
pearls at the end.   It is
full in this but the suit
that you see is semi stitched.  It was
n't stitched [MUSIC].
I have got it stitched.  So in this you will
get semi stitch.  It is a net fabric.  But
its color combination is very beautiful.
It has totally full zari work.  It is stone
work.  And it has embroidery on it.
You guys can see it.  The embroideries
look so beautiful [MUSIC].  Doing this
gives a very good look.  It is completely plain from the inside back.   There
is no design on the back.  Butt
front [MUSIC] is quite the design from the side.
And in this, at the bottom, you
get a border like this [music].  There is
such a design at the bottom and this type of border
is found attached.  [Music] So this overall look
of the kurti is very beautiful.  So I will
also share its demo with you all.
Now let us see its dupatta
which is very beautiful.
You can pair this scarf with [MUSIC] so many
outfits.  And
look, this dupatta has this type of border
attached to it.  And
such work is found in the entire dupatta.  This is a full work
dupatta.  It has complete thread sequence
work.  And look at the border.  This type has a
border attached to the edge.  It is
completely covered with pearls on one side.  These are the
types of embroideries [music].
This type of outfits look very good especially in functions.
So you can see that the
color of this dupatta is also very beautiful.  And
its length was also quite good.  The length of
this dupatta is very good.  [Music]
I really liked the length of it.  And right now
I'll share the demo of it with you guys
[music].  By
wearing both the outfits.  Now let me show you
[Sangeet] the
salwar which I got made,
I got straight pant made in this because it was semi stitched
so I got straight pant made in this
which is something like this you guys can see
[Sangeet] this is straight pant, I got it
made of this type only because
[Sangeet]
you could get it made as per your choice, I like
straight [Sangeet] pant with this type of kurta.
So now I am sharing with you guys a
demo of
what kind of look it provides after doing it.  You guys please
tell me in the comments which
outfits I look better in.  So
now I am with you guys because I have
shared both the outfits with you guys.
Now with this I show you that it is
always very important to choose jewellery with the outfit [music].
So what I've
chosen here is this jewelry.
You guys can see.
If anyone wants the link to this also then you guys can
comment me.  I will
provide you the link for this.  You can see.
[Music] It's
so beautiful and
this jewellery fits perfectly with both my outfits
[Music].  So you guys see and if
anyone has any queries related to this then
you can ask me.  Today I have
worn [sangeet] jewellery with this outfit which was looking very beautiful
and I liked its colour very much and
I will also show you the earrings that are with it.
With this one, I've got two earrings that [MUSIC].
This is not light, meaning it is not heavy.
[MUSIC] It's very light weighted.  Look, you were
very cute.  It was very light weight.  I
also liked its [music] color combination very much.
Now let me show you the look.
[Music]
So after wearing the first suit,
we get a look like this.  You guys
tell me how you like this look.
In the first outfit and this is the jewellery
which I have done and I am
sharing its demo with you all.  This is the look of the jewellery.
And this jewelry looked really good with this dress [MUSIC].
This is the suit.  You
can see.  Look at this combination, what a
lovely combination it is.  [Music]
This is the best option for festivals.   I liked it
very much.  Now you all
tell me by commenting how you liked this
outfit.  And this is the second outfit.
[Music] You guys can see my look in this.
How does it look after doing this?
How does this outfit look?  How does this jewellery look with it?
Please do let me know by commenting [Music].  Look,
this is the second outfit
in which a similar look has been created.
[Music] The jewellery also matched well with it
because the work on it was
of light pink colour [Music].
So thank you so much everyone.  Watch the video.